A Guide to the Richmond Symphony Archives, 1932-2009
Virginia Commonwealth University, James Branch Cabell Library
- Miscellaneous Documents 1933-1936, 1940-1941, 1959-2008 (Box 1-10)
  - Westminster Presbyterian Fellowship Hall 1988-1989 (Box-folder 9:38)
  - Westminster Presbyterian Fellowship Hall 1989-1990 (Box-folder 9:39)
  - Westminster Presbyterian Fellowship Hall 1990-1991 (Box-folder 9:40)
  - Richmond Symphony Endowment Campaign booklet 1989 (Box-folder 10 (oversized))
- Musicians 1986-1999, 2004 (Box 11-14)
  - 30 Candidates Information undated (Box-folder 11:1)
  - Alfonso, Sabrina undated (Box-folder 11:2)
  - Baldwin, Robert 1995-1997 (Box-folder 11:3)
  - Balter, Alen 1992-1997 (Box-folder 11:4)
  - Bay, Peter undated (Box-folder 11:5)
  - Ben-Dor, Gisele undated (Box-folder 11:6)
  - Bergman, Yaacov 1997 (Box-folder 11:7)
  - Blackwelder, Stephan 1996 (Box-folder 11:8)
  - Bond, Victoria 1997 (Box-folder 11:9)
  - Cole, Brian 2004 (Box-folder 11:10)
  - Comet, Catherine 1997 (Box-folder 11:11)
  - Cordle, David undated (Box-folder 11:12)
  - Cumming, Edward 1997 (Box-folder 11:13)
  - Curry, William Henry 1995-1997 (Box-folder 11:14)
  - Dackow, Sandra 1995-1996 (Box-folder 11:15)
  - Davenport, David 1994 (Box-folder 11:16)
  - Dunkel, Paul Lustig 1986-1997 (Box-folder 11:17)
  - Dunner, Leslie (one of five) 1997-1999 (Box-folder 11:18)
  - Dunner, Leslie (two of five) 1997-1999 (Box-folder 11:19)
  - Dunner, Leslie (three of five) 1997-1999 (Box-folder 11:20)
  - Dunner, Leslie (four of five) 1997-1999 (Box-folder 11:21)
  - Dunner, Leslie (five of five) 1997-1999 (Box-folder 11:22)
  - Dunner, Leslie 1998-1999 (Box-folder 11:23)
  - Edelstein, Gerardo 1996 (Box-folder 11:24)
  - Eddins, William 1996-1997 (Box-folder 11:25)
  - Every, Jack 1997 (Box-folder 11:26)
  - Felder, Harvey 1997 (Box-folder 11:27)
  - Fleischer, Randall C. 1997 (Box-folder 11:28)
  - Gittleman, Neal 1994-1998 (Box-folder 11:29)
  - Greenberg, Philip 1994-1998 (Box-folder 11:30)
  - Gunzen-Hauser, Philip 1991-1997 (Box-folder 11:31)
  - Hangen, Bruce undated (Box-folder 12:1)
  - Hanson, George 1990-1997 (Box-folder 12:2)
  - Heathplex, Bethany December 9, 1996 (Box-folder 12:3)
  - Hoffman, Jamin 1995-1996 (Box-folder 12:4)
  - HSU, APO 1996-1997 (Box-folder 12:5)
  - Hymes-Bianchi January, 1996-1997 (Box-folder 12:6)
  - Inouye, Derrick 1997 (Box-folder 12:7)
  - Itkin, David 1997 (Box-folder 12:8)
  - Jekowsky, Berry (one of seven) 1997-1998 (Box-folder 12:9)
  - Jekowsky, Berry (two of seven) 1997-1998 (Box-folder 12:10)
  - Jekowsky, Berry (three of seven) 1997-1998 (Box-folder 12:11)
  - Jekowsky, Berry (four of seven) 1997-1998 (Box-folder 12:12)
  - Jekowsky, Berry (five of seven) 1997-1998 (Box-folder 12:13)
  - Jekowsky, Berry (six of seven) 1997-1998 (Box-folder 12:14)
  - Jekowsky, Berry (seven of seven) 1997-1998 (Box-folder 12:15)
  - Jeter, John 1996 (Box-folder 12:16)
  - Jordania, Vantang 1995 (Box-folder 12:17)
  - Kalmer, Carlos 1997 (Box-folder 12:18)
  - Katz, David 1994-1997 (Box-folder 12:19)
  - Kay, George Robert 1991-1997 (Box-folder 12:20)
  - Kielsing, Bruce 2004 (Box-folder 12:21)
  - Kuntzch, Mathias 1997 (Box-folder 12:22)
  - Leonard, Peter 1992-1997 (Box-folder 12:23)
  - Levy, Micah 1994 (Box-folder 12:24)
  - Lockington, David 1993-1997 (Box-folder 12:25)
  - Lockington, David 1995-1998 (Box-folder 12:26)
  - Lockington, David 1997 (Box-folder 12:27)
  - Lockington, David 1998 (Box-folder 12:28)
  - Loebel, David 1997 (Box-folder 12:29)
  - Lipari, Peter undated (Box-folder 12:30)
  - Lipsky, Arie 1992-1997 (Box-folder 12:31)
  - Manahan, George undated (Box-folder 13:1)
  - Malina, Stuart (one of five) 1997-1999 (Box-folder 13:2)
  - Malina, Stuart (two of five) 1997-1999 (Box-folder 13:3)
  - Malina, Stuart (three of five) 1997-1999 (Box-folder 13:4)
  - Malina, Stuart (four of five) 1997-1999 (Box-folder 13:5)
  - Malina, Stuart (five of five) 1997-1999 (Box-folder 13:6)
  - Malina, Stuart 1998-1999 (Box-folder 13:7)
  - Miller, David Allen 1994-1997 (Box-folder 13:8)
  - Millard, Januaryet 1997 (Box-folder 13:9)
  - Mills, Amy 1994 (Box-folder 13:10)
  - Musprat, Kirk 1993-1997 (Box-folder 13:11)
  - Morgan 1998 (Box-folder 13:12)
  - Morgan 1997-1998 (Box-folder 13:13)
  - Morgan 1997-1998 (Box-folder 13:14)
  - Morgan 1997-1998 (Box-folder 13:15)
  - Morgan 1998 (Box-folder 13:16)
  - Morgan 1997-2000 (Box-folder 13:17)
  - Nierenburg, Roger 1990-1997 (Box-folder 13:18)
  - Ohyama, Heiichiro undated (Box-folder 13:19)
  - Palmer, Michael 1994-1997 (Box-folder 13:20)
  - Palmer, Nicholas 1993-1997 (Box-folder 13:21)
  - Paul, James 1993-1997 (Box-folder 13:22)
  - Pollitt, David 1997 (Box-folder 13:23)
  - Post, Arthur 1993-1997 (Box-folder 13:24)
  - Polivnick, Paul (one of six) 1997-1998 (Box-folder 13:25)
  - Polivnick, Paul (two of six) 1997-1998 (Box-folder 13:26)
  - Polivnick, Paul (three of six) 1997-1998 (Box-folder 13:27)
  - Polivnick, Paul (four of six) 1997-1998 (Box-folder 13:28)
  - Polivnick, Paul (five of six) 1997-1998 (Box-folder 13:29)
  - Polivnick, Paul (six of six) 1997-1998 (Box-folder 13:30)
  - Polivnick, Paul 1998 (Box-folder 13:31)
  - Prinzing-Briggs, William 2004 (Box-folder 13:32)
  - Russell, John M. 1995-1997 (Box-folder 13:33)
  - Sanderling, Stefan 1994-1997 (Box-folder 13:34)
  - Schwartz, Benjamin 2004 (Box-folder 13:35)
  - Shames, Jonathon undated (Box-folder 14:1)
  - Shames, Jonathon Shames,1997 (Box-folder 14:2)
  - Shui, Lan 1997 (Box-folder 14:3)
  - Simoncic, Tara 2004 (Box-folder 14:4)
  - Smith, Andre Raphel 1992-1997 (Box-folder 14:5)
  - Smith, Kirk undated (Box-folder 14:6)
  - Smith, Mark Russell (one of five) undated (Box-folder 14:7)
  - Smith, Mark Russell (two of five) undated (Box-folder 14:8)
  - Smith, Mark Russell (three of five) undated (Box-folder 14:9)
  - Smith, Mark Russell (four of five) undated (Box-folder 14:10)
  - Smith, Mark Russell (five of five) undated (Box-folder 14:11)
  - Smith, Steven undated (Box-folder 14:12)
  - Stafford, Wilson Peter 1989-1997 (Box-folder 14:13)
  - Stern, Michael 1988-1996 (Box-folder 14:14)
  - Stewart, Robert 1997 (Box-folder 14:15)
  - Sunshine, Adrian 1997 (Box-folder 14:16)
  - Tamarkin, Kate 1989-1997 (Box-folder 14:17)
  - Tang, David James 2004 (Box-folder 14:18)
  - Temple, Beth undated (Box-folder 14:19)
  - Surveys (for Thackar, Markland) undated (Box-folder 14:20)
  - Thackar, Markland 1996-1998 (Box-folder 14:21)
  - Thackar, Markland 1997-1998 (Box-folder 14:22)
  - Thackar, Markland 1997-1999 (Box-folder 14:23)
  - Thackar, Markland 1997-1999 (Box-folder 14:24)
  - Thackar, Markland 1998 (Box-folder 14:25)
  - Thackar, Markland 1998 (Box-folder 14:26)
  - Tinkham, Allen 2004 (Box-folder 14:27)
  - Walter, Michelle undated (Box-folder 14:28)
  - Washburn, Nan 1994 (Box-folder 14:29)
  - Waters, Emory undated (Box-folder 14:30)
  - Westerfield, Richard 1997 (Box-folder 14:31)
  - Wichterman, Catherine undated (Box-folder 14:32)
  - Wilson, Hermanto 2004 (Box-folder 14:33)
  - Wilson, Dorian 1997 (Box-folder 14:34)
  - Wilson, Keri-Lynn 1995-1997 (Box-folder 14:35)
  - Witty, Diane 1995-1997 (Box-folder 14:36)
  - Wong, Samuel 1997 (Box-folder 14:37)
  - Wroe, David 1993-1997 (Box-folder 14:38)
  - Ya-Hui, Wang 1997 (Box-folder 14:39)
  - Yahr, Barbara 1992-1995 (Box-folder 14:40)
- Programs 1957-2002, 2005-2006 (Box 15-19)
  - Program (one of four) undated (Box-folder 15:1)
  - Program (two of four) undated (Box-folder 15:2)
  - Program (three of four) undated (Box-folder 15:3)
  - Program (four of four) undated (Box-folder 15:4)
  - Program 1993, undated (Box-folder 15:5)
  - Program 1957-April 1980 (Box-folder 15:6)
  - Program 1975-1979 (Box-folder 15:7)
  - Program 1979-1996 (Box-folder 15:8)
  - Program 1980-1981 (Box-folder 15:9)
  - Program 1981-1989 (Box-folder 15:10)
  - Program 1981-September 1987 (Box-folder 15:11)
  - Program December 1988-June 1994 (Box-folder 15:12)
  - Program 1990-1991 (Box-folder 15:13)
  - Program 1990-1999 (Box-folder 15:14)
  - Program 1994-2002 (Box-folder 15:15)
  - Program 1996-1997 (Box-folder 15:16)
  - Program July-December 1998, undated (Box-folder 15:17)
  - Program (one of two) 1998-2001 (Box-folder 16:1)
  - Program (two of two) 1998-2001 (Box-folder 16:2)
  - Program January-May, 1999 (Box-folder 16:3)
  - Program, Rep 2005-2006 (Box-folder 16:4)
  - Book 1, Richmond Symphony, Programs 1964-1967 (Box-folder 17:1)
  - Book 2, Richmond Symphony, Programs 1967-1970 (Box-folder 17:2)
  - Book 3, Richmond Symphony, Programs 1970-1972 (Box-folder 17:3)
  - Book 4, Richmond Symphony, Programs 1972-1974 (Box-folder 17:4)
  - Book 5, Richmond Symphony, Programs 1974-1976 (Box-folder 17:5)
  - Book 6, Richmond Symphony, Programs 1976-1978 (Box-folder 17:6)
  - Book 7, Richmond Symphony, Programs 1978-1980 (Box-folder 17:7)
  - Book 8, Richmond Symphony, Programs 1981-1983 (Box-folder 18:1)
  - Book 9, Richmond Symphony, Programs 1983-1985 (Box-folder 18:2)
  - Book 10, Richmond Symphony, Programs 1985-1987 (Box-folder 18:3)
  - Book 11, Richmond Symphony, Programs 1987-1989 (Box-folder 18:4)
  - Book 12, Richmond Symphony, Programs (Part 1) 1989-1990 (Box-folder 18:5)
  - Book 13, Richmond Symphony, Programs (Part 2) 1989-1990 (Box-folder 18:6)
  - Book 14, Richmond Symphony, Programs 1990-1991 (Box-folder 18:7)
  - Book 15, Richmond Symphony, Programs 1991-1992 (Box-folder 18:8)
  - Book 16, Richmond Symphony, Programs 1992-1993 (Box-folder 18:9)
  - Book 17, Richmond Symphony, Programs 1993-1994 (Box-folder 19:1)
  - Book 18, Richmond Symphony, Programs 1994-1995 (Box-folder 19:2)
  - Book 19, Richmond Symphony, Programs 1995-1996 (Box-folder 19:3)
  - Book 20, Richmond Symphony, Programs 1996-1997 (Box-folder 19:4)
  - Book 21, Richmond Symphony, Programs 1997-1998 (Box-folder 19:5)
- Board of Directors / Executive Committee 1986-1991 (Box 20)
  - Binder 1, Board of Directors (Roster of those in attendance of meetings, schedules of when next meeting will be, etc.) 1988-1989 (Box-folder 20:1)
  - Binder 2, Board of Directors (Roster of those in attendance of meetings, schedules of when next meeting will be, Financial Statement, etc.) 1989-1990 (Box-folder 20:2)
  - Binder 3, Board of Directors (Documentation of meetings, roster of those in attendance, roster of members, Financial Statement, etc.) 1990-1991 (Box-folder 20:3)
  - Binder 4, Board of Directors/Executive Committee (Notification of meeting, balance statements, annual fund report, etc.) 1990-1991 (Box-folder 20:4)
  - Binder 5, Executive Committee (Interview notes, balance sheets, financial plans, etc.) 1986 (Box-folder 20:5)
  - Binder 6, Executive Committee (Interview notes, balance sheets, financial plans, etc.) 1987-1988 (Box-folder 20:6)
  - Binder 7, Executive Committee (Interview notes, balance sheets, financial plans, etc.) 1988-1989 (Box-folder 20:7)
  - Binder 8, Executive Committee (Interview notes, balance sheets, financial plans, etc.) 1989-1990 (Box-folder 20:8)
- Newspaper Clippings and Articles 1965, 1970, 1972, 1980-1998 (Box 21-25)
  - Binder 1, Clippings and articles about the Richmond Symphony January 1989-May 1989 (Box-folder 21:1)
  - Binder 2, Clippings and newspaper articles about the Richmond Symphony December 1989 (Box-folder 21:2)
  - Binder 3, Clippings and newspaper articles about the Richmond Symphony December 1989 (Box-folder 21:3)
  - Binder 4, Clippings and newspaper articles about the Richmond Symphony 1990 (Box-folder 22:1)
  - Binder 5, Clippings and newspaper articles about the Richmond Symphony July 1990-June 1991 (Box-folder 22:2)
  - Binder 6, Clippings and newspaper articles about the Richmond Symphony 1991-1992 (Box-folder 22:3)
  - Binder 7, Clippings and newspaper articles about the Richmond Symphony 1994-1995 (Box-folder 22:4)
  - Binder 8, Clippings and newspaper articles about the Richmond Symphony 1995 (Box-folder 23:1)
  - Binder 9, Clippings and newspaper articles about the Richmond Symphony 1995 (Box-folder 23:2)
  - Binder 10, Clippings and newspaper articles about the Richmond Symphony 1997 (Box-folder 23:3)
  - Binder 11, Clippings and newspaper articles about the Richmond Symphony 1997-1998 (Box-folder 23:4)
  - Newspaper clippings (1 of 2) undated (Box-folder 24:1)
  - Newspaper clippings (2 of 2) undated (Box-folder 24:2)
  - Newspaper clippings 1958-1961, undated (Box-folder 24:3)
  - Newspaper clippings April 10, 1961-November 25, 1965 (Box-folder 24:4)
  - Newspaper clippings October 7, 1969-February 24, 1970 (Box-folder 24:5)
  - Newspaper clippings February 16, 1970-October 22, 1972 (Box-folder 24:6)
  - Newspaper clippings April 26, 1980-March 26, 1982 (Box-folder 24:7)
  - Newspaper clippings 1980-1989 (Box-folder 24:8)
  - Newspaper clippings 1980-1984 (Box-folder 24:9)
  - Newspaper clippings September 1, 1981-December 9, 1981 (Box-folder 24:10)
  - Newspaper clippings April 5, 1982-January 21, 1989 (Box-folder 24:11)
  - Newspaper clippings January 13, 1982-December 10, 1982 (Box-folder 24:12)
  - Newspaper clippings January 1983-March 31, 1983 (Box-folder 24:13)
  - Newspaper clippings April 1, 1983-March 4, 1984 (Box-folder 24:14)
  - Newspaper clippings March 21, 1984-June 20, 1985 (Box-folder 24:15)
  - Newspaper clippings June 22, 1985-December 29, 1985 (Box-folder 24:16)
  - Newspaper clippings January-May 1986 (Box-folder 24:17)
  - Newspaper clippings January 3, 1986-April 6, 1986 (Box-folder 24:18)
  - Newspaper clippings June-August, 1986 (Box-folder 24:19)
  - Newspaper clippings September-December, 1986 (Box-folder 24:20)
  - Newspaper clippings January-April, 1987 (Box-folder 25:1)
  - Newspaper clippings May-September, 1987 (Box-folder 25:2)
  - Newspaper clippings October-December, 1987 (Box-folder 25:3)
  - Newspaper clippings January-February, 1988 (Box-folder 25:4)
  - Newspaper clippings May-September, 1988 (Box-folder 25:5)
  - Newspaper clippings July-August, 1988 (Box-folder 25:6)
  - Newspaper clippings August 22, 1988-January 1989 (Box-folder 25:7)
  - Newspaper clippings September-October, 1988 (Box-folder 25:8)
  - Newspaper clippings November-December, 1988 (Box-folder 25:9)
  - Newspaper clippings 1990-1994 (Box-folder 25:10)
  - Newspaper clippings 1993-1996 (Box-folder 25:11)
- Board Meeting Minutes 1936, 1975-1984, 2007 (Box 26)
  - Binder 1, Board Meeting Minutes 1936 (Box-folder 26:1)
  - Binder 2, Board Meeting Minutes 1975 (Box-folder 26:2)
  - Binder 3, Board Meeting Minutes 1976 (Box-folder 26:3)
  - Binder 4, Board Meeting Minutes 1977 (Box-folder 26:4)
  - Binder 5, Board Meeting Minutes 1978 (Box-folder 26:5)
  - Binder 6, Board Meeting Minutes 1979 (Box-folder 26:6)
  - Binder 7, Board Meeting Minutes 1980 (Box-folder 26:7)
  - Binder 8, Board Meeting Minutes 1981 (Box-folder 26:8)
  - Binder 9, Board Meeting Minutes 1982 (Box-folder 26:9)
  - Binder 10, Board Meeting Minutes 1983 (Box-folder 26:10)
  - Binder 11, Board Meeting Minutes 1984 (Box-folder 26:11)
  - Binder 12, Board Meeting Minutes 2007 (Box-folder 26:12)
- Scrap Books 1932-1933, 1964-1969, 1992-1993, 1998-1999 (Box 27-28)
  - Binder 1, Scrap book 1932 (Box-folder 27:1)
  - Binder 2, Scrap book 1932-1933 (Box-folder 27:2)
  - Binder 3, Scrap book 1964-1965 (Box-folder 27:3)
  - Binder 4, Scrap book 1965-1966 (Box-folder 27:4)
  - Binder 5, Scrap book 1967-1968 (Box-folder 28:1)
  - Binder 6, Scrap book 1968-1969 (Box-folder 28:2)
  - Binder 7, Scrap book 1992-1993 (Box-folder 28:3)
  - Binder 8, Scrap book 1998-1999 (Box-folder 28:4)
- Photography 1993 (Box 29)
  - Binder 1, Color photo slides of performances 1993 (Box-folder 29:1)
  - Binder 2, Photo contact sheets and photo negatives undated (Box-folder 29:2)
  - Binder 3, Photographs/Slides of George Manahan undated (Box-folder 29:3)
  - Binder 4, Photographs of the Orchestra, Sinfonia, Small Ensembles, and Youth Orchestra undated (Box-folder 29:4)
- Administrative Documents 1985, 1991, 1996 (Box 30)
  - Binder 1, Materials ranging from news clippings, agreements, and proposals 1985 (Box-folder 30:1)
  - Binder 2, Papers filed under Board Retreat, miscellaneous office paperwork 1985 (Box-folder 30:2)
  - Binder 3, Richmond Symphony Foundation (Papers explaining the guidelines of, letters refereeing to meeting minutes, raising funds, etc.) 1991 (Box-folder 30:3)
  - Binder 4, Negotiations (Minutes, management proposals, union proposals, press clippings) 1985 (Box-folder 30:4)
  - Binder 5, Negotiations (Minutes, management proposals, union proposals, press clippings) 1996 (Box-folder 30:5)
- Miscellaneous Binders 1990-1991, 2005-2009 (Box 31)
  - Binder 1, 50th Anniversary Planning (Project worksheets, planning, budgets, folders including information for two composers) 2007-2008 (Box-folder 31:1)
  - Binder 2, Correspondence to and from Catherine Wichterman regarding performances, fundraising, etc. 1991 (Box-folder 31:2)
  - Binder 3, Correspondences of Tom Philions regarding concerts, resignation letters, etc. 1990 (Box-folder 31:3)
  - Binder 4, Operations (Memorandums, master agreements, committee meeting minutes, calendars) 2005-2007 (Box-folder 31:4)
  - Binder 5, Season, Current (Master Agreement and Member Handbook) 2006-2007 (Box-folder 31:5)
  - Binder 6, Season Planning (Calendar and tentative dates for performances) 2008-2009 (Box-folder 31:6)
- Audio Videos, Cassette Tape, and Compact Discs 1990, 1993, 1995-2004, 2006 (Box 32-34)
  - Take 6 (video) undated (Box-folder 32:1)
  - Untitled (video) undated (Box-folder 32:2)
  - Richmond Symphony (video) undated (Box-folder 32:3)
  - Pops in Outer Space (video) undated (Box-folder 32:4)
  - "One" Richmond Symphony & Lewis and Clark (video) undated (Box-folder 32:5)
  - Mark Russell Symphony (video) undated (Box-folder 32:6)
  - Richmond Symphony "Masterworks" (video) undated (Box-folder 32:7)
  - The Greensboro Orchestra (video) undated (Box-folder 32:8)
  - Richmond Symphony "Richmond Scores Week" (video) undated (Box-folder 32:9)
  - Paul Polivnick 11/19 (cassette) undated (Box-folder 32:10)
  - Richmond Symphony "Family Concert Series" (cassette) undated (Box-folder 32:11)
  - Richmond Symphony-Creative Services (cassette) undated (Box-folder 32:12)
  - Richmond Symphony-Creative Services (cassette) undated (Box-folder 32:13)
  - Aretha Franklin-VA Symphony (cassette) undated (Box-folder 32:14)
  - Richmond Symphony- "Fredericksburg Concert" (cassette) undated (Box-folder 32:15)
  - WRVA-Springtime (cassette) undated (Box-folder 32:16)
  - Richmond Symphony-Fredericksburg Concert Series (cassette) undated (Box-folder 32:17)
  - Richmond Symphony Youth Orchestra with the Richmond Boys Choir (compact disc) undated (Box-folder 32:18)
  - Richmond Symphony Youth Orchestra with the Richmond Boys Choir (compact disc) undated (Box-folder 32:19)
  - Showcase: The Richmond Symphony undated (Box-folder 32:20)
  - Richmond Symphony, Campaign for Endowment, (video X2) July 1990 (Box-folder 32:21)
  - Richmond Symphony, Jim Nabors/The Chieftains, (video) March 10, 1997 (Box-folder 32:22)
  - Richmond Symphony, "Orchestrating a Better Tomorrow" (video X5) March 10, 1997 (Box-folder 32:23)
  - Richmond Symphony, At the Commonwealth Club (video) March 12, 1997 (Box-folder 32:24)
  - Richmond Symphony, Handel's Messiah (video) November 7, 1997 (Box-folder 32:25)
  - Richmond Symphony, Young Performers Program, Winter Concert (cassette) February, 9, 1993 (Box-folder 32:26)
  - Richmond Symphony, Young Performers Program (cassette) May 16, 1995 (Box-folder 32:27)
  - Richmond Symphony, Young Performers Program (cassette) November 28, 1995 (Box-folder 32:28)
  - Richmond Symphony, Young Performers Program (cassette) May 14, 1996 (Box-folder 32:29)
  - Richmond Symphony, Spring Concert (cassette) 1997/1998 (Box-folder 32:30)
  - Richmond Symphony, Subscription Sales (cassette) July 25, 1997 (Box-folder 32:31)
  - Richmond Symphony, Concert (cassette) 1997/1998 (Box-folder 32:32)
  - Richmond Symphony, Masterworks Concert (cassette) May 5, 1997 (Box-folder 32:33)
  - Richmond Symphony, Bernadette Peters (cassette) January 14, 1998 (Box-folder 32:34)
  - Richmond Symphony, Double Exposure (cassette) March 12, 1998 (Box-folder 32:35)
  - Richmond Symphony, Youth Concert Orchestra (compact disc) 1997/1998 (Box-folder 32:36)
  - Richmond Symphony, Vienna Boys Choir (video) 1998 (Box-folder 33:1)
  - Richmond Boys Choir, Raw Footage Dub (video) January 24, 1998 (Box-folder 33:2)
  - WWBT, Early News (video) March 18, 1998 (Box-folder 33:3)
  - Richmond Symphony, Richmond Scores Week (video) September 14, 1998 (Box-folder 33:4)
  - Richmond Symphony, Gershwin (video) September 25, 1998 (Box-folder 33:5)
  - Richmond Symphony, Halloween Spooktacular (video X2) October 19, 1998 (Box-folder 33:6)
  - Richmond Symphony, Messiah/Let it Snow (video) November 10, 1998 (Box-folder 33:7)
  - Richmond Symphony, Masterworks (video) November 10, 1998 (Box-folder 33:8)
  - Richmond Symphony, Charlie Chapman's "Gold Rush"/ Boys Choir & RS Youth Orchestra (video) December 14, 1998 (Box-folder 33:9)
  - Richmond Symphony, WCVE Sponsorship (video) 1998/1999 (Box-folder 33:10)
  - Richmond Symphony, Youth Orchestra- Boys Choir (video X6) January 9, 1999 (Box-folder 33:11)
  - Steve and Eydie (video) February 1, 1999 (Box-folder 33:12)
  - Richmond Symphony, Movie Magic/Masterworks (video) January 18, 1999 (Box-folder 33:13)
  - Richmond Symphony, Masterworks (video) March 3, 1999 (Box-folder 33:14)
  - Richmond Symphony, St. Matthew Passion" (video) March 22, 1999 (Box-folder 33:15)
  - Richmond Symphony, 1999-2000 season (video) September 2, 1999 (Box-folder 33:16)
  - Richmond Symphony, Duke Ellington (video) September 15, 1999 (Box-folder 33:17)
  - Pine of Rome, Conductor Mark Russell Smith (video) September 20, 1999 (Box-folder 33:18)
  - Richmond Symphony, Halloween Spooktacular (video) October 8, 1999 (Box-folder 33:19)
  - Richmond Symphony, The Messiah (video) November 18, 1999 (Box-folder 33:20)
  - Richmond Symphony, Jennifer Holiday Concert (video) December 9, 1999 (Box-folder 33:21)
  - Richmond Symphony, Marvin Hamlisch (video) December 9, 1999 (Box-folder 33:22)
  - Richmond Symphony, Masterworks (cassette) March 13, 1998 (Box-folder 33:23)
  - Richmond Symphony, Youth Orchestra (cassette) March 22, 1998 (Box-folder 33:24)
  - Richmond Symphony, Ben Vereen (cassette) March 23, 1998 (Box-folder 33:25)
  - Richmond Symphony, Youth Orchestra with the VA Youth Symphony (cassette) May 10, 1998 (Box-folder 33:26)
  - Richmond Symphony, Spring Concert (cassette) 1998, 1999 (Box-folder 33:27)
  - Richmond Symphony, Gold Rush (cassette) December 14, 1998 (Box-folder 33:28)
  - Richmond Symphony, Fall Concert (cassette) October 20, 1998 (Box-folder 33:29)
  - Richmond Symphony, Winter Concert (cassette) December 1, 1998 (Box-folder 33:30)
  - Richmond Symphony, Randy Newman (cassette) April 10, 1999 (Box-folder 33:31)
  - Richmond Symphony, The Flying Karamazov Brothers (cassette) March 29, 1999 (Box-folder 33:32)
  - Richmond Symphony, Young Performers Concert (compact disc) March 22, 1998 (Box-folder 33:33)
  - Richmond Symphony, Youth Orchestra, 1998/1999 Season (compact disc) March 30, 1999 (Box-folder 33:34)
  - Steve Lawrence and Eydie Gorme (compact disc) January 21, 1999 (Box-folder 33:35)
  - Richmond Symphony, Youth Concert Orchestra Sinfonia Concert (compact disc) March 21, 1999 (Box-folder 33:36)
  - Richmond Symphony, Spring Concert (compact disc) May 16, 1999 (Box-folder 33:37)
  - Richmond Symphony, Fall Concert (compact disc) November 23, 1999 (Box-folder 33:38)
  - Richmond Symphony, Barber Martin (video) November 15, 2000 (Box-folder 34:1)
  - Richmond Symphony (video) December 21, 2000 (Box-folder 34:2)
  - Richmond Symphony, Kathy Mattea (video) February 14, 2001 (Box-folder 34:3)
  - Richmond Symphony, Kathy Mattea (video X2) February 22, 2001 (Box-folder 34:4)
  - SMC (video) August 1, 2001 (Box-folder 34:5)